Balázs Buri

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Name Balázs Buri Born 1981 June 27

Address 1048 Budapest, Lakkozó street 31.

Phone +36 20 483 6003 E-mail buribalazs@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Strong communication skills with fluent English. Front-end development using AngularJS and other client side technologies (HTML5, LESS, JS, D3). Design experience (Look & Feel and controls) in video games, mobile games, websites, and music videos. Four year project management experience with a group of four people. Meeting tight deadlines for demanding clients often in different time zones. Worked as a freelance entrepreneur for three years on end to end project deliveries.

EXPERIENCE

2015 - CNW Rendszerintegrációs Zrt.

Front-End development for corporate software.

Complex user interfaces, localisation, validation, permission management.

Data visualization with D3 using large datasets.

Working closely with JAVA Server-Side development team. Agile, SCRUM

2011 - 2014: Freelance design and software deployment on web, iOS, Android using the

OpenFL platform.

UX design for video games and presentation software. Building look & feel from ground up. Modifying and improving existing solutions. Prototyping and testing.

2007 - 2011: Amega Team Kft.

GUI/UX design, Webdesign, Project management, Branding and logo design

2009 - 2011: Independent contractor with Soap Creative on various projects

Flash development, Actionscript3 programming

2003 - 2007: Freelance on various music video projects in Hungary

Post production, Digital matte, 3D environments, Rendering

2001 - 2003: Grant Reklám Kft.

Graphic designer for offline campaigns. Newspaper ads, Billboards

EDUCATION

2003 – 2007: Eszterházy Károly College, Diploma with Bachelor Degree

Teacher of Arts and Visual Communication

2001 – 2003: Eventus College, Electronic arts and 3D rendering

SKILLS

- Excellent communication skills
- Team player
- JavaScript, AngularJS, Grunt, D3
- Jira, IntelliJ IDEA, Balsamiq, Photoshop, 3DSMAX, Sony Vegas
- Software ergonomy
- Photo and video editing and composition
- Cinema Studies
- Sound mixing and optimisation for web and mobile

LANGUAGES

English: Advanced Hungarian: Native